Hi guys. I'm going to be vlogging this
week.
>> Sure. And I had a lot of things planned,
like outdoor plans, but I didn't realize
that it's raining, like pouring rain for
the next week. So, I think we're just
going to be having a little rainy day
vlog, which is fun. But, um, I have some
activities planned. And I also um Oh
yeah, I guess I should probably address
um whatever's going on here. I did get
an eyebrow piercing and it I think it's
projecting. So sorry that you have to
look at that cuz I literally keep wiping
it but it just keeps bleeding and I also
have a black eye now if you can't tell.
Like it's forming for sure. So that's
really awesome. Um, I also got this
piercing, which is also probably
rejecting. And I got my belly button
reierced, which is great because I've
been waiting to be done having kids, to
get my belly button reierced, and I'm
finally done having kids. So, but guys,
the eyebrow piercing hurts so bad. It
like I could feel the needle when she
was poking it through. I could feel it
like scraping
my skull and it was like such a gross
feeling. But anyway, um I really want to
show you guys my little project, this
little art project that I did. I'm very
proud of it. I think I've outdone
myself. And it's a little gift for Sunni
and Micah. And I'm waiting for Micah to
be done pooping so that I can show them.
And I'm very excited.
>> I'm very excited, too.
>> You are?
>> Yeah.
>> Are you all done playing in the rain?
>> I'm going to show the camera my little
project. Okay. You just chill out here.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Did I just do dogs myself? I actually
haven't seen it yet, so I'm like really
excited. Let me just explain.
So, I got a book from Shutterfly, which
is God damn, I keep doxing myself. I got
a book from Shutterfly, which is like a
make your own book website. Sunni reads
books all the time, of course, before
bed, before her nap every day. So, I
made her her own little book about her.
But, I used oil pastels and I just took
a photo of every like drawing that I
did. This is the cover.
Oh my god. Okay, I put a little photo of
her in here and I wrote her like a
little message. Sunni May.
[screaming]
Okay, that's all you get so far. Oh my
god. Came out so good. Wow. Okay. And
then I just like put some photos at the
end because it wouldn't allow me to do
the amount of pages that I wanted to do.
So, I just like didn't know what to do
and I put some photos at the end. But, I
think it came out really cute. I'm so
excited. I highly recommend
doing this for your child because it's
very fun. This will be something that
she can like look back on and be like,
"Dang, best mom ever." You know?
>> Mom was getting us a gift.
>> Okay, you guys. I worked really hard on
this.
>> It's a gift for both of you because your
guys is like most like this is the
activity you guys do together most.
>> Oh my god.
>> What is it? Painting
>> a book. drawing a book
>> that I wrote and illustrated all by
myself and I'm going to read it to you
guys. It's story time, you guys.
>> Wait, how did you do this actually?
>> Oh, wait. There's like a message at the
beginning.
>> Okay. Are you ready?
>> I'll read it really fast. For my
beautiful, perfect baby. It's been the
biggest blessing to be your mom. You
teach me new things every day and you've
grown me so much. I'm honored. I'm so
honored to be your mommy.
A
>> Sunni made
plays all day.
>> It's a bear.
>> Yes.
>> My gosh. When Sunni wakes up, her hair
is crazy. Mommy brushes it so it doesn't
stay tangly.
>> Bars.
>> Uh Sunni eats breakfast made by daddy.
He makes her yummy food and it makes her
happy. Or those peas.
>> They're cucumbers.
>> Those are cucumbers.
>> Yeah.
>> Wa! Micah, you're wearing the exact same
outfit. [laughter]
That's crazy.
>> Oh my god. Why are my arms bigger than
my leg? Okay, [laughter] what are you
trying to tell me?
>> Then she takes a nap with all her
friends. Sunni and daddy eat cheese in
bed. Then she takes a nap
and lays down her head. That's what it
could have been.
>> Mickey.
>> Sunni has a little brother named Mickey.
>> That's Mickey. Mommy,
>> that's like actually real life. You're
so happy to see him all the time.
>> Him. Look at him.
>> He doesn't do much yet.
>> Look at him.
>> So, that was kind of like funny like
little uh interruption in the the
rhyming flow. It's like it's supposed to
be like jarring like
>> this is the bridge the rest of the
course. Then Sunni rides in the car with
mommy. They like to go shopping and get
coffee. Mommy coffee. Nice. When Sunni
gets home, she takes a bath. with
bubbles and toys. Splish splash bars.
>> Sunni eats dinner and brushes her teeth.
Then she lays down in bed and goes to
sleep. Good night, Sunni.
>> Oh my gosh,
>> look at that.
>> Look, you're wearing the same outfit
again. [laughter]
>> Oh,
>> okay. So, what do you think?
>> N again.
Does that mean you like it?
>> And again, I do like it.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> You can do another one.
>> Beautiful.
>> Now I have Now I have
>> Now you have it.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, are you going to surprise us with
it? She's copying me.
>> Now I have
book.
>> What?
>> What did you write?
>> Oh, we definitely need to make one for
Mickey at some point now.
>> Yeah. Guys, speaking of Mickey, he's
been learning to crawl recently. I've
been in training with him and I saw this
like life hack that teaches your baby
how to crawl. It's basically like you
take a blanket, right? Lay them on the
blanket and then you just go like that
and it like helps him crawl. [laughter]
>> So, look, he's crawling.
>> Are you dead ass, bro? [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. And so you kind of just like
>> Oh my god.
>> No, it look watch out. [laughter]
>> You just lifted him up. This can't be
for real, dude.
>> Learn to like use his arms cuz right now
he kind of just like launches himself
with his legs.
>> Okay, Sunni is sleeping. It's still
pouring rain outside. So, Micah had an
idea to make Sunni some press on nails.
She's always asking me to paint her
nails. I lost her nail polish. I've been
looking everywhere for it. So, we got
her these little tiny press on. Look at
how cute they are. And we're going to
put 3D um designs on them. We're gonna
make them personalized to her.
>> Yeah, we're gonna make them really epic.
Kind of like that. It's a little teaser.
>> Except way better than whatever that is
supposed to be.
>> I've been practicing. So,
>> no, you haven't. That's the last time
you did anything.
>> That's me practicing.
>> So, you'll do one hand and I'll do one
hand.
>> Okay. I probably have a little bit of an
advantage because I know all of Sunni's
favorite animals and I think my hand is
going to be like animal themed.
>> I know all of her animals, too.
>> Name one of them. Five favorite animals
since you have five.
>> Hippo.
Cat,
lion,
>> bunny.
>> Yeah, there you go. Not in that order,
but yeah,
>> you you tell me then.
>> Monkey, fish, frog. [snorts]
Yeah.
>> Oh you're right. Monkey, and frog.
Those are good.
>> Mhm.
>> Dang it.
>> We should do a who knows Sunni better
[laughter]
video. Oh my god, you're already eating
with the bunny.
>> Whoever's nails she likes more wins. Oh,
that is very cutesy.
Wow. It's crazy how I'm just
automatically like so goated. [laughter]
Never even done this before. Look at
that. It's
>> so irritating actually. [laughter]
>> What the actual are you doing?
>> Guess the nail.
>> Is it a volcano?
>> It's in a Wow.
>> I thought you were doing animals.
What is that, dude?
>> Oh my god, you guys. I'm actually
eating. I'm going to go ahead and show
my nails cuz I just finished all of mine
while Micah finishes his for the thumb.
We have the Miffy.
Then we have the starfish.
Do you see it? Then we have this one,
which is just a little heart. Then we
have this panda.
And then last but not least, Pingu.
Well, it's not Pingu. It's Pingu's
little brother, but I forgot his name.
>> Tell me about each one. So, this one I
turned into I I liked abstract art, so I
just did a little abstract art with this
guy.
>> Is it like a portal?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> This is That was supposed to be like a
panda or something, but let's say it's a
clown now cuz it's got the weird ears.
>> This one's Mickey.
>> Oh, it is Mickey.
>> This guy looks like
>> That's cute, Micah.
>> He You got to get him from this angle to
you can see his face. He's kind of going
through it.
He's like dead. Oh, okay.
[snorts and laughter]
>> What about him?
>> I was trying to make a spider or like an
octopus with all the legs
>> like a ladybug.
>> You did really good.
>> So did you.
>> I'd almost say I'd give you the win
except that I like mine better.
>> Do you really? [laughter]
>> We're going to put them under sleep.
>> Close your eyes.
I have a surprise for you.
>> Oh, you said close your eyes and she
just went right back to bed.
>> It's a perfect
>> close your eyes. Close your eyes.
>> Close your eyes. Close your eyes.
[laughter]
Like the sweetest no ever. Remember,
Sunni, you were like, "I want you guys
to do my nails while I'm sleeping."
Do you remember you said that?
Yeah.
>> Such a sweet bonding moment.
Do we all feel really bonded right now?
I feel super bonded.
>> Shut up. Go like this. Wow.
>> Looks so good.
>> So beautiful.
>> Amazing. Okay, I want you to tell me
what do you think each thing is. So,
let's see. What's this?
>> Bunny.
>> Yes.
Okay. And then what's this?
>> Star.
>> Yeah.
>> Starfish.
>> And then what's this?
>> Yes. And then this
>> yard.
>> And then what's this one?
>> Penguin.
>> Wow.
>> Penguin. Okay. Okay. Now, what's this?
>> I don't know.
What's that?
[laughter]
>> Um, you know what? I don't know either.
>> What was that? Let's
>> ask Daddy.
>> What was that again? What did we come up
with? Portal.
>> A portal.
>> Portal. Sunni. Portal.
>> Portal.
>> Yay.
>> What's this?
>> Penguin.
>> Penguin. Sure. Sure. Why not? What's
What's this? [laughter]
It's not a penguin.
>> Penguin.
>> Another penguin.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Okay. What about that guy?
>> A snowman.
>> Oh, a snowman. That would have been a
good one to do.
>> Yeah.
>> And white guy.
>> She said white guy.
>> Sunni. That one's Mickey.
>> It's supposed to be Mickey. Daddy did
these ones. Mommy did these ones. Which
ones do you like better?
>> This one. [laughter]
>> So, this one's Mickey. Okay. Okay.
>> This one's a clown.
This one is a little animal man.
And this one is a sad man.
>> What the is a little animal man?
>> This guy's a sad dude. I don't know
what's happening to him. He looks like
he got smacked and he just fell over.
He's laying down and he's sad.
>> That's not fun.
>> This is like a whirlpool or maybe it's
like a some sort of it's abstract art.
>> Fun.
>> I don't know. Forget about those. Now
that you've had a little explanation,
what do you think is what do you like
more now? Which one do you like the
most? Which hand?
>> Look,
>> you got your nails.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, even though you like mama's
hand better, what do you think is the
best nail overall? What's your favorite
nail?
>> This one. Yeah. But what what specific
nail? Because maybe the Mickey nail is
your favorite.
>> Maybe this one.
>> Maybe that one. Maybe the bunny.
>> Yeah,
>> that is cute. Maybe that one. Or maybe
the Mickey nail. Look how cute it is.
>> So, what do you think's your favorite
nail? Which one's your favorite nail,
you think?
>> Hey.
Hey.
Hey guys, sorry to interrupt the video,
but this is really important.
I got my first sponsor.
>> Okay, you can leave.
>> As many of you know by now, I'm in the
process of buying a house. And I didn't
realize until now how important having a
good credit score is.
Like, I never owned a credit card in my
entire life. That's embarrassing. That's
why I started using Chime's credit
building card to finally start building
my own credit score. It's a secured Visa
credit card, so there's no interest and
no credit check to apply, which makes
the whole process super easy for someone
like me. I'm also moving our savings
over to Chime because their high yield
savings account is currently earning
3.75%
APY. I just learned what that means
today. It means your money actually
earns you more money. So, the higher the
APY, the better. Chime's APY is nine
times the average national savings rate
and significantly higher than what I was
previously saving. But my favorite
feature is the 5% cash back in your
mostused category, which you get to
choose yourself. Of course, I'm always
grocery shopping for my children. So, I
love that I can choose groceries as my
5% cash back category [music] on each
month. 5% cash back. That's $5 for every
$100 that I spend. If you want to check
out Chime, use the link in my
description and get your money up, not
your [music] funny up. Thank you, Chime,
for sponsoring this video.
>> That's not how you're supposed to open
them.
>> What do you mean?
>> You're supposed to like pop it on the
counter.
>> What do you mean you pop it?
>> That's how these cans work. You You pop
it.
>> Like you go like this. Like
>> Holy
>> Okay. Well, now it's falling out.
>> Okay.
>> Wait. Here, guys. We're going to make
pizza for our little rainy day.
I want to make pizza.
>> Yeah.
>> Soon you say pizza.
>> Pizza.
>> Wait, did you wash your hands?
>> You didn't really get your I did
[laughter]
>> her fake [clears throat] nail.
>> Sunni, wash your hands. Wait, where are
>> Oh no,
>> she's missing another nail.
>> Jesus.
>> Land it.
>> Wait, let daddy do it first.
>> Mine do it.
>> All right, [snorts] mine do it.
>> Good job.
>> Okay, my do it.
>> M do it. My do it.
>> Hey, she said my do it.
>> Okay. [laughter]
>> Oh my god.
>> Stop. [laughter]
Stop. D. Deal with your nail.
>> Wait. What type of pizza are you trying
to make?
>> This is such a bad idea to do the nails
before we did the pizza.
>> Yeah, it should have been the other way
around. It's okay, Sunni. Mommy will buy
you some like nail glue.
>> Look, I am a surgeon.
Let daddy get it.
>> Holy you guys suck at this. Wow,
you guys. That was really
>> I want to make it like a P songs.
>> What did you just say?
>> What did she just say?
>> Poke songs.
>> What's that?
>> I don't know.
>> You don't even know.
>> Is so good at making pizza.
Sweetie, you are crazy.
>> That's really good.
>> Look at our pizza, guys. Are you ready
to put it in the oven?
>> No.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, I'll do it.
>> I do it.
>> No, I don't think you should. No
offense.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> Wow. Can I try it?
>> No. Sunni, it's so beautiful. Shall we
cut into it?
>> Yeah.
>> Dude, I feel like we should make this
like a weekly thing. Pizza.
>> Wow. Guys, should we pray?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Who should we pray to?
>> Julie and Daddy.
>> I'm not praying to you guys. Dear Ariana
Grande, bless this meal.
Yeah.
Okay, your turn.
Did she just speak in tongues?
>> Wow, guys.
>> She has the gift of the Holy Spirit
dinner in her.
>> Okay. Holy this looks so good. I
think that the only thing that could
make this better is like onion, garlic.
I should have put garlic, but it's okay.
Wow. Mickey actually got you some food,
too. That's like the best pizza I've
ever had. Mickey, I got you this. It's
uh it's beef with kale and sweet potato
pouch.
Mickey, do you like it?
>> He just nodded at me.
>> Ew, bro. It's like he's pooping out of
his mouth. [laughter]
That actually looks like his poop, too.
Okay, I feel bad. Stop feeding it to
him. I got another one. Should we try
that one? [laughter] I got a green bean
one for him.
>> What?
>> [laughter]
>> This can't be right for a baby.
>> Did you hear me?
>> Organic sweet potato grass-fed beef.
It's They fed the grass beef. No, wait.
>> Oh my god. Hey, he looks like he's
falling, bro. [snorts and clears throat]
[laughter]
>> It's slowly going below the table.
>> Dude, pick him up then. Damn.
>> [laughter]
>> Next, you know, he's going to be like
just under the table.
>> Yeah, Micah. So, pick him off. Look,
he's struggling.
>> Why is he slowly going lower?
>> Mickey, can you say mama?
>> Okay, I want to watch anything eat while
I eat the food, please.
>> Okay,
>> guys. We were just playing an epic game
of hide and go seek and we came across
this little guy.
>> [laughter]
>> Show mommy him.
Hold him.
>> Okay. Hold up. Hold out your hand.
>> Okay. Show mama.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I got it. Okay.
[laughter]
>> I'm scared of him. Oh [laughter] god.
>> No, he's he he's he of you.
>> Oh no, he jumped out.
>> Okay. Okay,
>> everyone stay cool. [sighs and gasps]
>> How did he get in here, dude? I swear to
God, Mimi, I did not put him in here.
>> I don't.
>> I'm sorry. I just like don't like
animals.
>> It was so cute how she put him down.
>> Bye, my Mickey P.
>> Bye.
Seven. Eight.
>> Hey, you can't move it.
>> Ready or not,
[laughter]
>> in the closet.
>> That's not how the game works. Okay,
I'll go hide. I'll [laughter] show you
how that works.
>> This is so funny.
>> You stay in the hide spot.
>> Just shot out like a rocket, dude.
>> [laughter]
>> I just watched Obsession last night and
like I can't get it on my head.
>> Like Sunni running at me kind of freaked
me out.
>> Sunni's a little bit like the girl from
Obsession.
>> Yeah,
>> she'll get really mad if we like stop
playing with her or like leave the room
or something like that.
>> Okay, count all the way to [laughter]
10.
[snorts]
[laughter]
>> I find you.
>> Dang it.
Oh, she's counting.
>> Okay, you go hide.
>> Oh,
>> YAY. [laughter]
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, NINE, SEVEN.
[laughter]
>> Let's go find him.
Bro, why' she run like that? Dang. I
wonder where daddy is. [screaming]
[laughter]
>> What the is your head
give me enough time, [laughter]
>> dude?
[laughter]
[crying]
>> Oh,
it woke up Mickey.
>> Okay, wait. Blaring king.
[laughter]
>> 2.
>> He was smiling.
>> Is he pranking us [laughter] right now?
>> He looks like he's like, "I got you,
Got you to come over here and rub
my boy."
Who want to sit in this door
with me and rub my boy? Don't
Don't look at me like that.
>> Whoa. Stop.
[laughter]
>> She like sounds like she's cursing him.
>> Don't cast spells on him.
>> Watch him start levitating in there.
[laughter]
>> Time to make hide.
>> It's time for Mickey to hide.
>> Yeah.
>> Dang. That's actually a good idea. He
can hide anywhere.
>> Okay, I'm going to go hide Mickey.
>> What? [laughter] He needs to go to bed.
>> Count to 10. Okay.
>> Where's mommy?
>> Nice try. But mama's not there.
>> He's
in the closet.
[laughter]
[crying]
>> So funny seeing Mickey like spllayed
out. [laughter]
Oh, you want me to hide it again?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. 1 2 3 four.
>> No,
>> you skipped five.
>> One,
[laughter]
[snorts]
>> three,
>> two, three.
>> Four.
>> Five.
>> Six.
>> Say six.
>> Seven.
>> Uh. Six. Seven.
>> Six. Seven.
>> [snorts]
[laughter]
>> Eight.
>> Nine. 10.
>> 10. Okay.
>> Okay. Where do you think he is?
>> I don't know.
>> Okay. Well, you have to find him or else
then he can't go to bed.
>> Okay.
>> Do you think he's in the bathtub?
[laughter]
Oh my god. Look in there.
>> I found you.
>> You found me.
>> Whoa. Why is he like half your height?
What is going on? Wa!
>> He's getting riled up, dude. He's not
going to go to bed now.
>> Let's Let's try to see if he'll crawl
now. Go find Mickey.
[laughter]
>> He's standing there.
>> Yeah, that was scary.
>> Oh, Mickey. He was literally almost
crawling. Mickey, try to crawl again.
Like this. [sighs and gasps]
Mickey, you do this. Mickey, do you do
this?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like that. God's like
this.
>> Oh, he's not doing it anymore.
Sunni, look at this. Mickey's crawling.
>> Come here.
Come here.
He's trying so hard.
>> He's doing it.
>> He's really trying.
>> Oh my god. He's doing it.
>> There's a wall.
>> You have to break through. You have to
punch through the wall with your mind.
>> You got it. Yes. Yes. [laughter]
No.
No,
>> Sunni, you're messing it up. You almost
had.
>> Good morning. Sunni and I are both roomy
today from K-pop Demon Hunters. Let's
show them.
>> Did you got a Dutch braid like me?
>> No, I just have a regular braid. Um,
we're about to go on a run though. We've
been running every morning. Update on my
eyebrow piercing. [laughter]
My black eye is just getting worse. So
yeah.
>> That's not That's not English. Go get in
your stroller.
>> No.
>> And we're going to go on a run.
>> I'm going to get
>> Ask daddy.
>> The calm before the storm.
Uh you want to walk us through kind of
like what's the routine? What's the What
are we looking at? I don't know what I'm
doing, Alex. [laughter]
I've never looked into like the correct
way to run or anything. Like, I just run
and I hope for the best. I don't get
shin splints.
>> Yeah, that's cuz you're young.
>> Wait till you get to my age, bro.
>> In [laughter] high school, I used to try
running and I would get shin splints all
the time.
>> Oh, you Yeah.
>> My dad told me that you have to make no
sounds with your feet when you run.
>> No sounds.
>> His a little trick like try to like land
soft. So,
>> so the other day we were stretching for
a run and then I dropped into like
>> one of those
>> one of the Thank you.
>> like that and I pulled my groin muscle
my right like that's what it's called I
guess like this.
>> Yeah.
>> And I couldn't run that day. Then I was
filming an ad read and I did the thank
you thank you at the end of it and I
repulled it and then my manager was like
you can't even put that in anyway. So I
did that all for nothing. I'll insert
the clip here though. [snorts]
Wait.
>> Oh, me. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you.
I did it. I wanted to add the thank
[laughter] you. Thank you to my ad.
>> Anyway, so
>> is this your way to put that footage
back in?
>> Yeah. Is this a good one?
>> That's pretty good.
>> Normally, we run like a mile and then
I'm like I'm done after that cuz I
cannot do that much. Bro, I literally
just got the ick.
>> What about this?
>> Okay.
>> Does this change it? Switch it back.
>> Attraction restored.
>> Dude, Kenzie from Love Island really
inspired me to like really lock in this
year. Try to get my splits. I've never
been able to do the splits. Maybe that's
why I'm so anxious. She was saying like
in your groin there's a lot of tension
built up in there. You got to release
it.
So,
>> I don't have an issue with that.
>> I think the pizza is not like the pizza
we ate last night. Not helping.
>> You want to record mom and dada?
>> Yeah. I'm just doing me. I'm
of the trees.
>> Okay.
>> Look at those trees.
houses,
trees. It's raining and mommy.
>> Is that epic?
>> A.
>> So, we basically had to stop.
>> I got a sideache.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, now I'm really upset.
>> Do you hear that cheese? This vlog
sucks. Let's see what our best mile was.
So, that was a 26 minute mile and a
half.
>> It's like almost worse than like a
walking mile.
>> Yeah. Okay, we got a mile run. That was
10 minutes.
>> Hey,
>> that that's okay. What do you think? Is
that good?
>> Yeah, it's not that's not bad. I think
typically you want to get a six mile run
is kind of like the goal. That's like a
good run. Yeah, but 10 minutes is only
like
>> 4 minutes away.
>> Okay. I think like because we just
started getting back into running.
That's like pretty freaking good.
>> No. Okay. Well,
>> where did you get him?
>> Uh, from outside.
>> From outside. Is he alive?
>> Yes.
doesn't look alive.
You know who would love to see that?
>> Mama. I think mama.
>> No,
>> I think mama wants to see him. Sunni,
maybe you go up to mama and you and you
give it to mama.
>> No. [laughter]
>> Mommy,
>> it's yours.
>> Mommy said no.
>> Maybe mama wants to hold him.
>> Mommy said no. Hold him.
Yeah. Hi, little cicada.
>> Hi.
>> What's your name?
>> Cic.
My name is Cicada Bug.
>> Oh, wow. Uh, what do you like to do for
fun?
>> Swing around on swing with my friend
bugs.
>> Wow.
>> With my cicada bug friends.
>> That's really cool.
I love your heart.
>> That
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> I love your heart.
>> Wow.
>> Hi,
>> I'm Finger.
>> Um, I'd like to be your friend and I
want to swing with you.
>> Wow. Are you guys swinging?
>> Yes.
>> Hey, Cicada.
>> There's a baby over there crying.
You should go check him out.